All right, Team Rocket again here
with project number two, task board.
So, here, the problem
that we were trying to solve is that
with many projects, there remains to be
open-ended tasks without fixed deadlines,
which get frequently neglected.
This task board integrates task weighting
directly into a visual progress bar,
which you will see on the output screen.
Okay, and so, yeah,
as you can see here, we have a progress
bar at the top.
We have the Kanban board over here,
and as we move items into In Progress,
you can see that it's starting
to progress the board.
And then when we move items to Done,
then you start seeing a new board get --
or I should say, a new progress bar
begin to fill.
Right, so with this, we did keep it
simple,
and we did have to cut future features,
which we hope to implement in the future.
One of which is multi-tenant authorization
and complex multi-board workspaces
to nail multi-faceted projects.